Association of Canadian Publishers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Subject files, 1951 - 1984; F-57-5; 4.91 m of textual records ca. 50 photographs; Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-57-5-1-3 Physical description: 26 photographs located in F-57-5-9-11
  - General files, 1974 - 1983; F-57-5-9; 1.27 m of textual records
    - D, E - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-84 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Edmonton School Board, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-85 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Employment Programs, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-86 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Experience Program: OAC Summer Employment, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-87 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Film Workshop - Festival of Festivals, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-88 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Freedom of Information, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-89 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - Freedom to Publish, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-90 (Archival box - standard 57-51)
    - French Book Displays, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-91 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - F - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-92 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Government of Canada, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-93 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Governor Generals Award, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-94 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Graphic Arts Industries Association, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-95 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Greey Realty (lease), 1981; F-57-5-9-0-96 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Grolier Ltd., 1981 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-97 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Groundwood Books, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-98 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - G- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-99 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Harlequin Books, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-100 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - H- Miscellaneous, 1980 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-101 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Independent Bookstores, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-102 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - India: World Book Fair, 1977 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-103 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Industry, Trade and Commerce Department - AECB, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-104 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Industry, Trade and Commerce Department - Correspondence, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-105 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Industry, Trade and Commerce Department - Foreign Fairs, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-106 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Industry, Trade and Commerce, Department - Small Business, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-107 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Institute of Canadian Publishing (Proposed), 1977; F-57-5-9-0-108 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Interdidact - International Fair for Educational Materials, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-109 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - International Board of Books for Young People, 1977; F-57-5-9-0-110 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - International Year of the Child, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-111 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - International Youth Library, 1977; F-57-5-9-0-112 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Jerusalem Book Fair, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-113 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Lang, Michenrer, Farquarson and Wright, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-114 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Law and Business Publications, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-115 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Learned Societies' Conference, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-116 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Libraries - American Library Association, 1977 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-117 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Libraries - ACP/TPL Study, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-118 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Libraries - Canadian Library Association, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-119 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Libraries - American Library Trustees, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-120 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Libraries - C.A.L.U.P.L., 1981; F-57-5-9-0-120 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Libraries - Ontario Library Association, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-121 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Libraries - Ontario Public Library Program Review, 1981 - 1983; F-57-5-9-0-122 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Libraries - Public Lending Right in England, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-123 (Archival box - standard 57-52)
    - Library Services Ltd., 1977; F-57-5-9-0-124 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Library Sound Services - proposed, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-125 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Limited Editions, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-126 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Literary Marketplace, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-127 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Lobbying and Interest Group Representation, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-128 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Lorimer, Jim - MS of The Politics of Canadian Publishing, 1976 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-129 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - L - Miscellaneous, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-130 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - McCarthy and McCarthy, 1977 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-131 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Ian MacDonald Library Services Ltd., 1977 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-132 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - McGill-Queens' University Press, 1980 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-133 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Maclean's Magazine, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-134 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Mailing List, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-135 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Manitoba Metis Federation, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-136 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Market Relations Co-ordinator, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-9-0-137 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Mass Market paperback survey, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-138 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Member Services Co-ordinating Committee, 1977; F-57-5-9-0-139 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Membership - Memoranda to, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-140 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Methuen Publishing Inc., 1977; F-57-5-9-0-141 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Metric Commission, 1975 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-142 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Ministry of State for Economic Development, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-143 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Montreal International Book Fair, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-144 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Multiple Schlerosis Read-a-Thon, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-145 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - National Book Centre, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-146 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - National Book Week / Festival, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-147 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - National Book Week / Festival, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-148 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - National Library - Book Deposit, 1977 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-149 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - National Museum of Man, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-9-0-150 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - National Museums of Canada, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-151 (Archival box - standard 57-53)
    - Nelson Canada, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-152 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - New Democratic Party, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-153 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Nonprofit organization, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-154 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - North Vancouver Community Arts Council, 1977; F-57-5-9-0-155 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Norway Translation Inquiry, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-156 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Ontario Career Action Program, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-157 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Ontario Ministry of Culture and Recreation, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-158 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Ontario Ministry of Education, 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-159 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Ontario Ministry of Education - Computer Committee, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-160 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Ontario Readers Survey, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-161 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Ontario Teachers Federation, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-162 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Ontario Youth Secretariat, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-163 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Paper Industry, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-164 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Pepperwood, Incorporated, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-165 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Periodical Distributors of Canada, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-9-0-167 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Peterson, Rein, 1977; F-57-5-9-0-168 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Plagiarism, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-169 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Postal Rates, 1975 - 1977; F-57-5-9-0-170 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Postal Rates, 1981 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-171 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Postal Strike Contingency Plan, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-172 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Press Releases, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-173 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Printing Industries of American, Incorporated, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-174 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Prison Arts, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-175 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Prisoners' Books, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-176 (Archival box - standard 57-54)
    - Project progress, Canadian Library Association, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-9-0-177 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Provincial Government Programs, 1978 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-178 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Public Lending Right, 1977 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-179 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - P - Miscellaneous, 1976 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-180 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Quebec, 1976 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-181 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Quebec Books in Translation, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-182 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Q - Miscellaneous, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-183 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Readers' Club, 1977 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-184 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Reading Survey - Weekend Magazine, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-185 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Rights Canada, 1980 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-186 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Royalties, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-187 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Sales Representatives and Distributors, 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-188 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Salon du Livre, 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-189 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Saskatchewan Department of Industry and Commerce, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-190 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Saskatchewan School Trustees Associaton, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-191 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Science Council, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-192 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Seattle Book Fair - interest in, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-193 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Secretary of State - Francis Fox, 1977 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-194 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Secretary of State - copyright, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-195 (Archival box - standard 57-55)
    - Secretary of State - Foreign Fairs, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-196 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Secretary of State - Multiculturalism, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-197 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Secretary of State - Publishing Advisory Committee, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-198 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Secretary of State - Project Feasibility Program, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-199 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Self Publishers, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-200 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Seminar Proposals and Plans, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-201 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Seminars, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-202 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Silcox, David - Director of Cultural Affairs, City of Toronto, 1974 - 1983; F-57-5-9-0-203 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Small Business Assistance Programs, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-204 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - W.H. Smith, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-205 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Social Science Federation of Canada, 1980 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-206 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Societe de Development du Livre, 1979 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-207 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Speech to the Association of Canadian Studies, 1979; F-57-5-9-0-208 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Speech Conference on Law and Communications, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-209 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Speech Publishers / Curriculum Conference, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-210 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Tax Incentives, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-211 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Technology Publications, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-212 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Telidon 1/3, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-213 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Telidon 2/3, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-214 (Archival box - standard 57-56)
    - Telidon 3/3, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-215 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Telidon, 1981 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-216 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Toronto - miscellaneous, 1981 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-217 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Toronto - Typographical Union, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-218 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Translation, 1977 - 1982; F-57-5-9-0-219 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Translation Contract, 1977; F-57-5-9-0-220 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Travel Books, 1977; F-57-5-9-0-221 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - T - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-222 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - U.S.S.R., 1975 - 1977; F-57-5-9-0-223 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - United Parcel Servic - dispute re: American Trucking Company, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-9-0-224 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - U.S.A. (1 clipping), 1981; F-57-5-9-0-225 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - University of Saskatchewa - Faculty List, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-9-0-226 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - University of Toronto, 1977; F-57-5-9-0-227 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - U - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981; F-57-5-9-0-228 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Vancouver School Board, 1977 - 1980; F-57-5-9-0-229 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Van Nostrand Reinhold, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-9-0-230 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Wolfe, Morris, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-9-0-231 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Women's Studies, 1978; F-57-5-9-0-232 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Writers Union of Canada, 1980; F-57-5-9-0-233 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
  - Working files, 1951 - 1984; F-57-5-10; 78 cm of textual records
    - Alberta Publishers Association, 1974 - 1981; F-57-5-10-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Association for the Export of Canadian Books, 1974 - 1983; F-57-5-10-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-57)
    - Association of Manitoba Book Publishers, 1975 - 1981; F-57-5-10-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association 1/2, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Atlantic Publishers Association 2/2, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-10-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Book Clubs - including Reader's Club, 1975 - 1978; F-57-5-10-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Book of the Month Club, 1977; F-57-5-10-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Background C-14 - list of Ontario Texts, 1951 - 1983; F-57-5-10-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Bill C-26, 1977; F-57-5-10-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Canada Council - Block Grant Program, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Canada Council - International Translation Grant Program, 1980; F-57-5-10-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Canada Council - International Translation Grant Program, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-10-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Canada Council - Translation Progam, 1980; F-57-5-10-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Canadian Books for College Stores, 1976; F-57-5-10-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Canadian Books Abroad - supply of, 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Canadian Books in Print, 1976; F-57-5-10-0-16 (Archival box - standard 57-58)
    - Canadian Books in Print - Analysis of data, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-10-0-17 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Books in Print - Analysis, 1977; F-57-5-10-0-18 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Books in Print - Publishers Index, F-57-5-10-0-19 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Film Development Corporation, 1979 - 1982; F-57-5-10-0-20 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies Abroad, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-21 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies Catalogu - ACP and CBPC, 1980; F-57-5-10-0-22 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies - External Affairs, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-23 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies - France, 1979; F-57-5-10-0-24 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies - Italy, 1980; F-57-5-10-0-25 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies - Japan, 1979; F-57-5-10-0-26 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies - Norway, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-27 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies - U.K., 1978 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-28 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies - U.S., 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-29 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Canadian Studies - West Germany, 1980; F-57-5-10-0-30 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Cataloguing in Publication - Audlye, 1974 - 1977; F-57-5-10-0-31 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Conseil Superior du Livre, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-32 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Co-publishing, 1976 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-33 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Co-publishing - National Museums, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-34 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Co-publishing - projects, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-35 (Archival box - standard 57-59)
    - Direct Sales, 1973 - 1977; F-57-5-10-0-36 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Export Assistance, 1977 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-37 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Government Support Programs Analysis, 1975 - 1977; F-57-5-10-0-38 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Grant Analysis: CC, BPP, OAC, 1975 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-39 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Grant Analysis Tables, 1983; F-57-5-10-0-40 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Kent Commission, 1981; F-57-5-10-0-41 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Loan Program Analysis - Ontario, 1976 - 1981; F-57-5-10-0-42 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Loan Review - Ontario Development Corporation, 1974 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-43 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - National Book Week, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-44 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - National Book Festival, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-45 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - New Press re Ontario Development Corporation, 1974; F-57-5-10-0-46 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Ontario Arts Council programs, 1977 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-47 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Ontario Government Policy, 1973 - 1978; F-57-5-10-0-48 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Ontario Government Relations, 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-10-0-49 (Archival box - standard 57-60)
    - Paper and Manufacturing Costs, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-10-0-50 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - P.O.C.A. Programs - Backlist, Canada Books, CRIC, 1974 - 1975; F-57-5-10-0-51 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Postal Rates Survey, 1979; F-57-5-10-0-52 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Postal Rates, 1981; F-57-5-10-0-53 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Quebec - Bill 51: Development of Quebec Firms in the Book Industry, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-54 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Quebec - Bill 101: Charter of the French Language, 1976 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-55 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Quebec Government and Cultural Policy, 1978 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-56 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Quebec definition of 'book', 1984; F-57-5-10-0-57 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Quebec Loan Program, 1975; F-57-5-10-0-58 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Quebec Publishers, 1978; F-57-5-10-0-59 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Saskatchewan - Government Relations, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-10-0-60 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Scholarly Publishing, 1973 - 1976; F-57-5-10-0-61 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Scholarly Publishing, 1976 - 1977; F-57-5-10-0-62 (Archival box - standard 57-61)
    - Secretary of State - Book Publishing Development Program 1/2, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-63 (Archival box - standard 57-62)
    - Secretary of State - B.P.D.P. 2/2, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-64 (Archival box - standard 57-62)
    - Secretary of State - B.P.D.P. clippings, 1979; F-57-5-10-0-65 (Archival box - standard 57-62)
    - Secretary of State - B.P.D.P. Discussion Paper Drafts, F-57-5-10-0-66 (Archival box - standard 57-62)
    - Secretary of State - B.P.D.P. guidelines, 1980 - 1982; F-57-5-10-0-67 (Archival box - standard 57-62)
    - Secretary of State - Foreign Fairs Committee - 1/2, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-68 (Archival box - standard 57-62)
    - Secretary of State - Foreign Fairs Committee - 2/2, 1980 - 1981; F-57-5-10-0-69 (Archival box - standard 57-62)
    - Secretary of State - Foreign Fairs Policy (I, T and Commerce Minister, Jack Horner), 1977 - 1978; F-57-5-10-0-70 (Archival box - standard 57-62)
    - Secretary of State - Multiculturalism Directorate, 1981; F-57-5-10-0-71 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Secretary of State - A Study of Book Publishing in Canada (Bureau of Management Consultants), 1976; F-57-5-10-0-72 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Seminars - A.C.P., 1980 - 1983; F-57-5-10-0-73 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Small Business Assistance, 1976 - 1979; F-57-5-10-0-74 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council (SSHRC), 1974 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-75 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - SSRC and HRCC Analysis of Grants, 1977; F-57-5-10-0-76 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Book Import Statistics, 1975; F-57-5-10-0-77 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Statistics - UK and Australia, 1979; F-57-5-10-0-78 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - US - Exports and Import Figures, 1979 - 1980; F-57-5-10-0-79 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Wholesalers Replies to IPA Survey, 1974; F-57-5-10-0-80 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Writers Contract drafts, IPA report, 1975; F-57-5-10-0-81 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Paul Audley unfiled correspondence received, 1974; F-57-5-10-0-82 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Paul Audley unfiled correspondence received, 1975; F-57-5-10-0-83 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
    - Paul Audley unfiled correspondence received, 1976; F-57-5-10-0-84 (Archival box - standard 57-63)
- Chronological files, 1974 - 1981; F-57-6; 63 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the day files of the IPA/ACP, arranged in chronological order. Included are correspondence originating from the IPA/ACP, financial statements, minutes, news releases and some Literary Press Group correspondence.
  - Chronological files, 1974; F-57-6-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 57-64)
  - Chronological files, 1975; F-57-6-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 57-64)
  - Chronological files, 1975; F-57-6-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 57-64)
  - Chronological files, 1977; F-57-6-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 57-64)
  - Chronological files, 1977; F-57-6-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 57-64)
  - Chronological files, 1977; F-57-6-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 57-64)
  - Chronological files, 1977; F-57-6-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 57-64)
  - Chronological files, 1977; F-57-6-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 57-65)
  - Chronological files, 1977 - 1978; F-57-6-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 57-65)
  - Chronological files, 1979; F-57-6-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 57-65)
  - Chronological files, 1979; F-57-6-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 57-65)
  - Chronological files, 1979; F-57-6-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 57-65)
  - Chronological files, 1979; F-57-6-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 57-65)
  - Chronological files, 1979; F-57-6-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 57-66)
  - Chronological files, 1979; F-57-6-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 57-66)